# **MATTEO GREGORICCHIO**

Email

Personal Site





matteo.gregoricchio at mail.com matteo.gregoricchio at libero.it www.matteogregoricchio.com https://it.linkedin.com/in/matteogregoricchio https://bit.ly/2JTv7LQ



Hi There! I'm Matteo, currently working for **DeltaTre** in Turin as a **Web Support.** Meanwhile I'm also studying at **Fondazione ITS** to graduate as a Software Developer with a Diploma of Higher Education.

The programming languages and IT topics I'm mostly working on are:

C#, Javascript, SQL and NO-SQL Databases, Cloud - Oriented Services (AWS and Azure Platforms).

I'm an **Art History Graduate**. During my studies I worked as a **freelancer translator** on the platform Upwork.

My best **traits & skills** are synthesis, precision and work organization. I'm independent and I'm really resolute. All those soft skills are required at my job at DeltaTre.

My main **interests** are contemporary art (with a focus on Latin America production), videogames, literature, the IT field (especially web programming) and the World Wide Web. Lastly, I'm a football fan!

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Web Support at DeltaTre

06/2018 - current

Monitoring of uefa.com and fifa.com sites during *live events* of those two associations. Use of monitoring equipment and tools developed by DeltaTre. I also work as I^ level technical support (in english) for operators/editors working during *live events*. Intermittent job.

#### **Freelance Translator at Techpump**

05/2015 - 12/2018

Translation projects eng-ita, online cultural contents.

### Internship at Polo Museale del Piemonte, Torino (TO)

11/2016 - 12/2016

Internship for Master's Degree. Employee at Education and Services Office. 150 hours.

### > Traineeship at Technical Office, Moruzzo (UD)

03/2014 - 05/2014

Archive catalogation at Technical Office, Moruzzo (UD). Stage part of Bachelor's Degree program.250 hours.

#### **EDUCATION**

Diploma of Higher Education for software development (Integrated Backend Services)

2018-2020, Fondazione ITS per le tecnologie dell'informazione e della comunicazione Main Courses and Programming Languages: .Net C# - PHP - Javascript & JQuery – Relational Databases SQL (sia Microsoft SQL Server sia MySQL) - Cloud Infrastructure

Secondary Courses: Java - No-Relational Databases NO-SQL (MongoDB) - Html&CSS - Project Management Basics (Waterfall, Agile)

**> Master's Degree, Art History** 

2015 - 2017, Università degli Studi di Torino [Final Grade: 110 e Lode/110] Dissertation: *Il conceptualismo ideológico nell'Argentina degli anni '70: analisi dell'operato del Grupo CAYC;* supervisors: José Luis de la Nuez Santana, Franca Varallo; topics: latin-american contemporary art, contemporary argentine art ('60-'70 of the 20th century).

**> Bachelor's Degree, Conservation of Cultural Assets** 

2011 - 2015, Università degli Studi di Udine [Final Grade: 108/110] Dissertation: *Julio Castellanos e i Contemporáneos;* supervisor: Mario Sartor; topics: latin-american contemporary art, contemporary mexican art ('20-'40 of the 20th century).

**> Secondary School Diploma** 

2006 – 2011, I.S.I.S. Vincenzo Manzini, San Daniele del Friuli (UD)

#### LANGUAGE COMPETENCE

► Italian: Mother Tongue

English: Professional KnowledgeSpanish: Professional Knowledge

### **IT COMPETENCE**

- **ECDL Certificate** n. IT 1049910, released from AICA on 25/01/2007.
- Advanced Knowledge of .Net C#, Relational Databases SQL, Cloud Infrastructure
- ≥ Good Knowledge of Javascript e jQuery, PHP, Html
- **Basic** Knowledge of Java, CSS, No-Relational Databases NO-SQL (MongoDB)
- **Advanced** Knowledge of **Windows** and **Apple Systems**.
- Advanced Knowledge of Microsoft Office and LibreOffice suites.
- **Advanced** Knowledge of **web surfing** and **web searching** and **e-mail systems**.

In compliance with the Italian legislative Decree no. 196 dated 30/06/2003, I hereby authorize you to use and process my personal details contained in this document.

Turin, 09/2019